&gt；&gt；Steve：所以我们的目标就是像使用FastDOM一样发出呼喊
&gt;&gt; Steve: So our goal was to then just
give a shout out like using FastDOM to
比如加速这些箱子。
like speed up these boxes.
在我们看到我们有一个大问题之前，我们通过分离所有的东西来解决它。
Before we saw we had a big problem,
we solved it by separating everything.
我们想要做的是回到我们的原始代码，因为，再一次，
What wanna do is kind of go back to
our original code because, again,
我们试图解决的问题是，
the problem that we're
trying to solve here is,
是的，如果你能把它分开很酷，那就去做，对吧。
yeah, if you could separate it cool,
do it, right.
但是如果你有一个功能，那就是非常
But if you have one
function that's being very
负责所有的阅读和写作。
responsible about doing all of
its reading and its writing.
然后你有另一个函数，它们被彼此调用，
And then you have another function and
they get called after each other,
你刚才做了什么？
what did you just do?
你读了一堆，你写了一堆，你读了一堆，你写了一堆，对吧？
You read a bunch, you wrote a bunch, you
read a bunch, you wrote a bunch, right?
在给定的函数中，您可以完全优化它，但是
In a given function,
you could totally optimize this, but
在您的应用程序中？
across your application?
除非你是故意的，
It's gonna happen unless
you are purposely,
除非你有某种抽象来管理它。
unless you have some kind of
abstraction managing this.
所以我们将回到更接近我们的原始代码的东西。
So we'll go back to something
a little closer to our original code.
所以让我们把这个处理掉，
So let's get rid of this,
去吧把那个放回去。
go ahead and put that back there.
实际上也抓住了那条线。
Actually grab that line as well.
我也可以在双倍宽度上保持这一切。
I could keep that all on
the double width as well.
我只是，把它改成这样更容易。
I just, was easier to change it like this.
所以在这里我们可以继续，我们可以说
So here we can go ahead and we could say
最终是快速测量。
fastdom.measure, eventually.
给它一个函数来测量它。
Give it a function to measure it.
&gt；&gt；Steve：然后我们可以通过说
&gt;&gt; Steve: And
then we could schedule a write by saying
快写，或者说是变异。
fastdom.write, or mutate rather.
&gt；&gt；steve：酷，去做吧。
&gt;&gt; Steve: Cool, go ahead and do it.
看看能不能用。
See if it works.
没有犯任何错误，这是一个受欢迎的变化。
Didn't make any mistakes
which is a welcome change.
&gt；&gt；Steve：我们将打开它，转到性能。
&gt;&gt; Steve: We'll open it up,
go to performance.
我们要测量它。
We're going to measure it.
&gt；&gt；steve：它会停止的。
&gt;&gt; Steve: And it will stop.
你可以看到，就像我注意到的第一件事是有一点，
And you can see like first thing
I notice is there's a little,
那里有点小颠簸，对吧？
some little bumps there, right?
不是那么大的钉子。
It's not that big spike.
但是动画，是的，我们可以在那里锁定整个线程。
But the animation, yeah,
we can lock up the entire thread there.
多次按下一个按钮，
With hitting a button multiple times,
简单的事实是，我没有达到每秒60帧的速度，这一点很有帮助。
the simple fact that I am not hitting
it 60 frames per second is helpful.
但是我们继续，拿一个在这里，看看它。
But we go ahead, grab one of these here,
take a look at it.
而且我们绝对不会再打击这个领域了。
And we are definitely not
thrashing the dom anymore.
好的，所以这是一种有用的方式，
All right, so it's a useful way to,
我们有一个问题，我们可以应用解决方案。
we have a problem we can
kind of apply the solution.
因为是的，去找出你的代码可以采用的每一条代码路径
Cuz yeah, going and figuring out every
code path that your code can take and
确保两个函数不会在
making sure two functions
aren't doing their own thing in
与世隔绝将会很难。
isolation is going to be hard.
但是我们有一个抽象，我们只记录我们所有的测量和
But we have an abstraction where we
just record all of our measurements and
然后我们将所有的变种批处理在一起，我们可以相当容易地解决这个问题。
then we batch all of our mutates together,
we can solve this problem fairly easily.